The atmosphere of real Italy rules the mood at our restaurant.We offer you not only the best recipes of typical Italian dishesalso the mood of many things: interior, music, waitresses andjust Italian air! We put our hearts and souls into every dish wecook to help you feel the vibes of Italy, and to transport you tothe picturesque scenes of ancient times.  Come join usfor a lunch, a dinner or a drink.

Sun‒Thurs 7am‒11am (breakfast)Sun‒Thurs 11am‒9pm (lunch) Fri & Sat 8am‒12pm (breakfast)Fri & Sat 12pm‒4pm (lunch)